{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873632.1341949, "questionText": "What do we know so far about immunity and COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Often , there are comparisons between COVID-19 and influenza because the symptoms are somewhat similar and because COVID-19 started to emerge in the winter , which is the same time of the year when we see influenza . But when it comes to immunity , there 's a very big difference between influenza and COVID-19 . With influenza , because of previous infections and vaccinations , there 's always a percentage of the population that is immune to infection — so they 're protected and wo n't get the flu that year . And there 's an even larger percentage of the population that has some immunity — not perfect immunity , so you 'll still get infected , but enough so that your symptoms will be relatively mild .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "dc866a30-7541-11ea-9f7e-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "dc88a46c-7541-11ea-997a-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "dc88a598-7541-11ea-92ae-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873632.933503, "questionText": "Why is it that older people are developing more severe symptoms than younger people , even though both groups have no immunity to COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "We do n't have a good answer for that yet . It certainly seems that people over the age of 60 , particularly those with secondary medical conditions , are at greater risk for severe disease . We 're beginning to understand that men may also be at increased risk . We 're seeing these trends pretty consistently across different countries . What we do n't know yet is why . That 's a really important area of research that my colleagues at Hopkins are working on . If we could better understand what 's happening in high - risk populations to make them more susceptible , it could inform development of treatments for severe disease .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "dd00611e-7541-11ea-a949-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "dd0061fa-7541-11ea-836b-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "dd006240-7541-11ea-89d4-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873633.683869, "questionText": "What 's the role of seasonality in the spread of this virus ?", "answerText": "A lot of respiratory viruses have a seasonality . In areas that have seasons , you often see more respiratory disease in the winter than in the summer . That 's because the conditions of lower temperature and lower humidity help facilitate transmission of the virus . COVID-19 is entering the population during the winter but we do n't know if it 's going to act like a typical respiratory virus in terms of seasonality . We do n't know if COVID-19 will be very dependent on winter to effectively transmit , like the flu , or if it will find ways to effectively transmit throughout the year .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "dd72e04a-7541-11ea-bb47-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "dd72e11c-7541-11ea-9367-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "dd72e162-7541-11ea-92f4-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873634.4516742, "questionText": "Are you concerned that we 'll see a dip in cases this summer and then see a resurgence next fall or winter ?", "answerText": "I think that 's a major concern . Nearer term , I 'm concerned about what will happen if public health interventions are loosened . Right now , public health interventions are doing a good job of reducing the number of cases , but we do n't know how long we will have to keep those measures in place . When we relieve them , there is always a potential for cases to spike again .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "dde808ac-7541-11ea-87f9-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "dde8099c-7541-11ea-9ea3-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "dde809e2-7541-11ea-b4f0-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873635.2056189, "questionText": "In addition to better understanding immunity and seasonality , what other aspects of COVID-19 are researchers trying to understand ?", "answerText": "We 're trying to understand how this virus is able to cause many more cases of mild disease compared to other viruses . We think that may be linked to why it 's so good at transmitting . We 're also trying to understand , once you 've had the virus , whether you 're safe to go out and work again because you have some level of protection .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "de5b13b0-7541-11ea-a6e9-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "de5b148c-7541-11ea-bfc9-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "de5b14c8-7541-11ea-b9e0-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/30/andrew-pekosz-immunity-seasonality/?fbclid=IwAR2LUcjr7Ltz6koe0IjRV3gr7E3tW0K6hqlcaYPtKQz3HBmjlQ7YRGrtgHw", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1585590600", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873635.9668229, "questionText": "How can people who have recovered from COVID-19 help researchers to understand immunity , seasonality , and other aspects of the virus ?", "answerText": "We need people to volunteer after they 've recovered to help us understand how their bodies have responded to the infection . Those types of studies are going to be so important because as we , hopefully , flatten the curve , we may have the opportunity to help people at the tail - end of the curve improve their prognosis based on findings from our study of people who were infected on the front - end of the curve .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "decf3a24-7541-11ea-8efa-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "decf3af6-7541-11ea-bf83-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "decf3b34-7541-11ea-8448-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873636.719452, "questionText": "What is the difference between self - quarantine , self - isolation , and social distancing ?", "answerText": "Self - quarantine is staying in place , either at home or elsewhere , for fourteen days because you have been exposed to someone who has tested positive for COVID-19 . Self - isolation would be isolating within the house after you start showing symptoms of COVID-19 . Social distancing is a response in which people remain home and distant from others ( such as by refraining from shaking hands or hugging or going to the store at off hours ) , without any known exposure to the virus , to limit possible transmission to or from others .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "df4211c0-7541-11ea-a900-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "df421288-7541-11ea-aab1-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "df4212cc-7541-11ea-8573-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873637.4628701, "questionText": "What are the signs or symptoms that someone should self - isolate ? When can the self - isolation end ?", "answerText": "If you do develop symptoms , like a fever , cough , or shortness of breath , that is when you would need to self - isolate at home , away from other household members . If you develop these symptoms , contact your medical provider but stay home as long as those symptoms are manageable ( like you would for a normal cold or flu ) . If you have severe shortness of breath or if symptoms suddenly get worse , that is when you should seek out medical care .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "dfb3817a-7541-11ea-b155-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "dfb3824c-7541-11ea-bd03-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "dfb3829c-7541-11ea-b932-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873638.2053518, "questionText": "What is the safest way to self - isolate one person within a larger household ?", "answerText": "If you can have a separate space for the sick person — a space where they can access the restroom without traveling through commons spaces — that would be best . Those who are caring for loved ones who are sick at home should wash their hands frequently , avoid close contact as much as possible , and have the sick individual wear a surgical or procedure mask to prevent droplets spreading through the air . It is also important to clean frequent- or high - touch surfaces , as well to clean clothes in very hot water . Caregivers should also wear a mask , if possible .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "e024ccb8-7541-11ea-ab6b-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "e024cd76-7541-11ea-8237-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "e024cdb4-7541-11ea-b50a-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873638.9622111, "questionText": "In households that are not able to accommodate these suggestions , what else can be done to limit transmission at home ?", "answerText": "If you 're not a caregiver , maintaining six feet of distance and washing your hands frequently are the main steps , along with cleaning surfaces often . If you are a caregiver , it 's certainly tougher . You should wear a mask if possible and follow the other guidelines of handwashing and cleaning clothes and surfaces frequently .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "e0984986-7541-11ea-9841-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "e0984a4c-7541-11ea-a950-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "e0984a8a-7541-11ea-be16-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873639.707872, "questionText": "How can parents and other caregivers help children and dependents who are unable to follow the recommended advice ( like washing hands and not touching your face ) , particularly if they need to be self - isolated ?", "answerText": "I think that 's a tougher situation . It 's very hard to stay away from kids , especially when they 're ill and need care and comfort . If possible , main caregivers should be those who are not at high risk from COVID-19 , meaning those not over age sixty or with underlying health issues . Other than that , it 's important to take the normal precautions in terms of handwashing and cleaning , but it is much more difficult with children .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "e10a10e8-7541-11ea-bf66-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "e10a11b0-7541-11ea-a8fe-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "e10a11f6-7541-11ea-bdf0-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873640.452995, "questionText": "How much can caregivers rely on childcare alternatives ( relatives , neighbors , babysitters ) in this moment ?", "answerText": "In general , it 's important to keep the circle smaller . At the moment , not exposing yourself to many additional people is best . Healthcare workers , people with critical jobs , and hourly employees who have to work will need to rely on childcare providers . In those situations , you may ask someone you know and trust , and who is reliable in taking the social distancing rules seriously . If possible , childcare providers should not be in a group that 's at high - risk for COVID .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "e17bc33a-7541-11ea-91b8-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "e17bc418-7541-11ea-ab4d-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "e17bc454-7541-11ea-a52b-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
{"sourceUrl": "https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/03/23/how-to-self-quarantine-self-isolate/?mc_cid=0ed1a231a3&mc_eid=9687fd9d33", "sourceName": "JHU HUB", "sourceDate": 1584946800, "lastUpdateTime": "1584979200", "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {}, "dateScraped": 1585873641.2019331, "questionText": "What supplies should be on hand , for both self - quarantine and self - isolation ?", "answerText": "For self - quarantine you should have your basic supplies like food and thirty days of any medications being taken . If you should become sick , and in anticipation of becoming sick , you should have supplies like Gatorade — something to rehydrate — as well as cough medicine to manage symptoms , and Tylenol to assist with the fever .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "e1ee0aa8-7541-11ea-b0b5-3af9d3ce0829", "answerUUID": "e1ee0b68-7541-11ea-9f4e-3af9d3ce0829", "exampleUUID": "e1ee0bae-7541-11ea-bfc9-3af9d3ce0829", "topic": "self-quarantine"}
